(Penny:)If you let her go, there is no way
you can find anyone else.
Speaking on behaIf of all women, it
is not gonna happen, we had a meeting.
(Raj:)And you.
(Penny:)A grown man fainting at the sight
of a little blood.
(Sheldon:)Excuse me,
this is a fairly substantial wound. You...
Amy. Amy.
(Sheldon:)Amy.
(Amy:)What do you want?
(Sheldon:)I was kind of hoping I could continue
vacationing in your laboratory.
(Sheldon:)After all, I did book the whole week.
(Amy:)Do you honestly think
you can just waItz back in here...
(Amy:)...after the way you behaved
yesterday?
I was not myseIf.
I had lost a lot of thumb blood.
- That's not an apology.
- That is your opinion.
(Amy:)I want a real apology.